http://www.collegegymfans.com/privacy.html

0.0
Around the NCAA (W)
0.0
Around the NCAA (M)
0.0
#1 to #12:
2020 Capsule Previews
0.0
#13 to #25:
0.0
NCAA (W)
0.0
NCAA (M)
0.0
FAQ:
General NCAA
0.0
FAQ:
Code and Rules
0.0
FAQ:
Recruiting
0.0
FAQ:
Championships
0.0
FAQ:
0.0
FAQ:
— Latest News
— Around the NCAA (W)
— Around the NCAA (M)
— Features
—— Capsule Previews
——— #1 to #12:
2020 Capsule Previews
——— #13 to #25:
— NCAA Links
—— NCAA (W)
—— NCAA (M)
— FAQs
—— FAQ:
General NCAA
—— FAQ:
Code and Rules
—— FAQ:
Recruiting
—— FAQ:
Championships
—— FAQ:
Records
— Site Help
—— Using the Site
—— Recruitables DB
—— FAQ:
Recruitables
— Contact the Site
Privacy Policy
CollegeGymFans.com Privacy Policy
Your privacy is important to CollegeGymFans.com.  This privacy statement covers the personal information that CollegeGymFans.com obtains, and the ways in which we intend to use that information.
Only information needed for the proper function of the site is collected.   Information you provide to this site will never be sold, traded or released to a third party except where required by a court of law or where necessary to defend CollegeGymFans.com in a court of law.
Information Collected
CollegeGymFans.com may collect and use the following:
Information that you provide as part of the registration process
Information provided by your browser during your normal use of this website
Information you provide directly to the site through posts, emails or the like
A "cookie" to store personalization information necessary for the operation of the forums, profiles, and customizable areas of the website
CollegeGymFans.com may use the personal information to:
Provide normal operation of the forums, profiles and other features of the website, including your access and use
Publish the information that you designate (your profile, your posts)
Personalize the website for you
Contact you only for issues related to your profile or the web site operation
In the normal course of business, we may need to disclose certain information to agents or subcontractors.  The agend or subcontractors will be obligated to abide to the terms of this privacy statement.
CollegeGymFans.com will make a best effort to take the technical and business precautions necessary to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information.  Information on the website will be stored securely, but content made available for public vieweing will be available to users throughout the world.
CollegeGymFans.com reserves the right to update this policy at any time via posting a new version.
CollegeGymFans.com is not responsible for the behavior of other users.  The site contains links to other sites.  CollegeGymFans.com is not responsible for the privacy policies or content of these other web sites.
For any further questions, please contact This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it.
Terms of Use
About this Site
Privacy Policy
(c) 2001-2020 CollegeGymFans.com
